https://www.womenscollegehospital.ca/privacy-policy

Care Programs
Coronavirus (COVID-19) Information for Patients and Visitors
PPE Donations during COVID-19
Access Centre
Acute Ambulatory Care Unit (AACU)
After Cancer Treatment Transition Clinic (ACTT)
Family Practice Foot Clinic
Family Practice Health Centre (FPHC)
Rheumatology Program
Sexual Assault/Domestic Violence Care Centre (SA/DVCC)
Substance Use Service
Surgery and Surgical Clinics
Wellness for Independent Seniors (WISE)
The Centre for WISE Practices in Indigenous Health
WIHV - WCH Institute for Health System Solutions & Virtual Care
Care Programs
Coronavirus (COVID-19) Information for Patients and Visitors
Access CentreAcute Ambulatory Care Unit (AACU)After Cancer Treatment Transition Clinic (ACTT)Atrial Fibrillation ClinicBay CentreBreast CentreCardiologyCentre for HeadacheCrossroads ClinicDermatologyEndocrinology and DiabetesEnvironmental Health ClinicFamily Practice Foot ClinicFamily Practice Health Centre (FPHC)Family Way Obstetrical GroupGastroenterology ClinicGeneral Internal Medicine ClinicsGynecologyMedical ImagingMental HealthNephrology ClinicOsteoporosisPain ProgramPeter Gilgan Centre for Women's CancersRespirologyRheumatology ProgramSexual Assault/Domestic Violence Care Centre (SA/DVCC)Substance Use ServiceSurgery and Surgical ClinicsWellness for Independent Seniors (WISE)Women's Virtual
A-Z Care Programs
Research, Education & Innovation
Research, Education & Innovation
Women's College Research Institute
Education at Women's College Hospital
The Centre for WISE Practices in Indigenous Health
WIHV - WCH Institute for Health System Solutions & Virtual Care
News & Publications
News & Publications
Patient Safety
WCH Connect
WCH Newsroom
Heather’s CEO Blog
Ways to Connect with Us
A Thousand Voices for Women's Health
General Statement
This privacy policy applies to the collections, uses and disclosures of personal information by Women's College Hospital ("Women's College" or "we") in connection with the Women's College Hospital website ("the website").
Women's College respects the privacy of visitors to the website. Any and all personal information collected at this site is kept strictly confidential and is only used for the purposes specified at the time of collection to which you consent; for such other purposes to which you may consent from time to time (the "Purposes"); and as required or permitted by applicable law. Personal information will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed, other than to third party service providers engaged to help us carry out the Purposes which are bound by agreement to protect your personal information; as required or permitted by law; to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual sale, merger, amalgamation or any other type of transfer affecting Women's College in order for you to continue to receive the same products and services from the third party; or to such other parties to which you may consent from time to time. You may withdraw consent at any time subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. If you wish to withdraw your consent at any time, please contact our Privacy Officer, at 416- 323-7702. We will inform you of the implications of withdrawing consent.
What is Personal Information?
Personal information is any information that is identifiable with you. This information may include but is not limited to your name, personal mailing address, personal phone numbers, and personal email address. Personal information, however, does not include your name, business title or business address and business telephone number in your capacity as an employee of an organization.
Protecting your Privacy
The privacy policy is current as of the "last updated" date which appears at the top of this page. Examples of the Purposes for which we collect, use and disclose personal information via the website as of such date are set out below. We recommend you review this privacy policy periodically. From time to time, we may make changes to this privacy policy with or without notice to you. We will treat personal information in a manner consistent with the privacy policy under which it was collected, unless we have your consent to treat it differently.
Feedback to the Site
At the website you are invited to send your feedback to the site. We may use this feedback to help us develop further content and features for the site. We will only use and disclose your name and email address to respond to your feedback. Due to the insecure nature of email communication, the Owner does not wish to use this website as a means of communication with the public or patients (i) regarding questions or issues of a medical nature; (ii) to establish physician/patient relationships; (iii) to book or cancel appointments; or (iv) for inquiries regarding fees, services or similar matters. Email communications regarding such matters or containing personal health information will not be responded to and will be destroyed. Accordingly, please ensure you do not include any personal health information or other sensitive personal information, including financial information, in emails.
Browser Information Collected on the Site
The website collects statistical information through a log file. This generates a monthly report that indicates which pages were visited and how frequently, referring pages, and IP addresses. Individual identities cannot be determined from these reports. The developers of this site use and disclose this information, including your IP address, to help us develop further content and features for the site.
Privacy Policies of Other Sites
The website provides links to many other sites. Some of these sites may use cookies to collect personal information or commercial data. Women's College is not responsible for the privacy practices of sites to which it links, and advises you to review the privacy policies of those sites when visiting such sites.
How to Contact Us
All comments, questions, concerns or requests, including access requests, regarding your personal information or our privacy policy and practices, should be forwarded to our privacy officer as follows:
In writing:
Privacy Officer Women's College Hospital 76 Grenville Street Toronto ON M5S 1B2
76 Grenville Street,
6 a.m. to 7 p.m.
PLAN YOUR VISIT
Directory – Floor Listings
The directory is your floor guide to the Women's College Hospital building.
DOWNLOAD (PDF)
Patient Handbook
Our Patient Handbook is your guide to Women’s College Hospital.
DOWNLOAD ENGLISH (PDF)
DOWNLOAD Français (PDF)
